Availability Zones or AZs and Regions are
可用性区域或 AZS 和区域是
the core components within AWS that allow local and global redundancy.
允许本地和全局冗余的 AWS 中的核心组件
Proper usage of these key resources is crucial for
正确使用这些关键资源对于
anyone building high availability systems on AWS.
任何人在 AWS 上建立高可用性系统
An AWS region contains multiple availability zones.
AWS 区域包含多个可用性区域
These availability zones allow for fault isolation within
这些可用性区域允许在
a region and provide the simplest way to achieve a significant level of redundancy.
并提供最简单的方法来实现大量冗余
The AWS global infrastructure is made up of
AWS 全球基础架构由
multiple geographic regions spread around the world.
多个地理区域分布在世界各地
These regions are connected via high speed private network,
这些区域通过高速专用网络连接
but the regions themselves are independent.
但这些地区本身是独立的
Availability Zones and regions our containers for AWS networking.
可用性专区和区域用于 AWS 联网的容器
Networking in AWS is setup via
在 AWS 中建立网络是通过
isolated Virtual Private Clouds or VPCs that exist in one AWS region.
隔离的虚拟专用云或 VPC 存在于一个 AWS 区域中
You will get to see how you can have multiple of
你会看到你有多大的
your own custom networks within AWS allowing you complete control and security.
AWS 中的您自己的定制网络 允许您完成控制和安全性
In this lesson, we will explore VPCs
在本课中 我们将探索 VPC
themselves and also the networking that is configured within them.
以及在这些网络中配置的网络